Minnesota Geological Survey Field Notebooks, 1877-1990
University of Minnesota Libraries
- Thiel, George A.
  - Cuyuna, 1925.; 3 volumes (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Cuyuna, 1925.; 4 volumes (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Marl, 1926, 1928.; 6 volumes (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - Cretaceous of Southern Minnesota, 1952. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Thomas, J.A.: Cloquet quad, 1958. (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Upham, Warren: Altitudes on railroads leading northward from Duluth, 1893 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Vishwanathan, Subramanian
  - Hibbing Sheet, 1968.; 2 volumes (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Brittidington, 1967. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1969.; 3 volumes (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
- Weiblen, Paul: "Masters Thesis,", 1960. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Weiss, Malcolm P.: Book 1-11, 1949-1951.; 11 volumes (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
- Wells, Francis G.: Rove Slate Area, 1927. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Werner, W.C.: Limestone Quarries, 1921. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Wheeler, James D.: Crane Lake (Traverse notes), undated. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Winchell, Alexander
  - Northern Minnesota, 1886. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Lake Huron, 1886-1887. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Zappfe, Carl: Cuyuna, 1906. (Box 24, Folder 5)